So I'm probably going to be shutting down
my business mentorship.
And before I get into that fully,
I'm not sure many of you actually
understand what
this mentorship's all about.
We talk about 10 grand months,
100 grand months, but
the reality is the majority of businesses
that I work with just want to make an
extra 2K a month. And
that two grand for them is enough
that they don't have
to worry about the mortgage.
They don't have to worry about the car
finance.
They don't have to worry about the grocery
bills.
But getting that 2K,
they don't want to drive Uber in the
evenings.
They don't want to get a second job where
they've got to start over again.
They already have skills in a department.
So you watching this,
it might be personal training,
might be a physio, might be an
accountant. And what you want to do
is you want to take what you're making now
and
generate a couple extra thousand a month.
And you want to do
that often by taking your skills online,
so that when you come
back from work, you can open your laptop.
When you have a client cancel,
there's something you can do.
And I think sometimes I'm guilty of
talking in millions
and everything like that,
when in reality, this course
is about spending a little bit so you can
make a
little bit, and then
that will compound over time.
Now,
there are going to be some success
stories. Ryan Moak, first met him in 2021.
He invested several hundred thousand
dollars into Nutonic this week.
So I mean, it's amazing
that sometimes I do just help people go
online, and they
make tremendous amounts of money.
But the reality is two grand a month for
you means you're getting your money back
in two months. Now, personally,
why I'm thinking of shutting it down
is I'm tired.
I am in this Discord all day, every day,
and what I've said to myself is, "I'm
going to keep doing this till the end of
the year." So for that, I've created an
offer.
I'm not willing to do this for less money,
so what I'm doing is I'm
shortening the amount of time you'll be in
the Discord.
So I'm taking it from 12 months to six
months.
There's going to be a link in the
description here.
And here's going to be my offer.
If you're not online in six months making
that
extra 2K a month from your 2.5K
investment,
in six months' time at the end of the
year, I'll give you your money back.
It's that simple.
Because let's say,
we're going to open this up to 100 people.
After 100 people, this offer goes away.
Let's say 90% of you are getting
that 2K a month. Cool.
That 10% of you go, "James,
I'm not there yet." I don't deserve to
keep the cash,
quite simply.
I ran a similar incentive a couple of
months ago,
and we took in 15 people,
and we didn't have one refund request, not
one. So I'm quite bullish on this.
I've also hired more people.
So when you get in the Discord,
we're now doing two coaching calls a week,
and you
can do this with Ollie, who
is my YouTube strategist.
He's doing my thumbnails, my titles.
He's doing all the testing.
And then Cam, I've just promoted Cam.
He was a student who then worked for me,
and I've just given him a pay rise because
he's that good,
and I don't want anyone to poach him.
These guys are doing two calls a week,
which we've added.
They're also in the Discord around the
clock with me, and we ran some data the
other day.
39% of all the messages in here are me,
which is why I'm getting
tired.
I'm thinking I'm only going to do this for
the rest of the year.
Other news as well is
that you would've seen that Nutonic,
we just
raised $6 million at a $60 million
valuation.
Now, what that means
is we're scaling aggressively.
We're going into retail in America.
We've just hired a load of new staff.
And without flexing,
my shareholder position
is already well into
eight figures,
and we're looking to scale that.
And the truth is,
I can't continue to be this tired all the
time.
By this time next year,
I don't think I can do this every day.
I don't think it'll be worth it for me
either.
Yeah, sure, making 100K a month,
whatever it is, fine.
But Nutonic's now at the scale where it's
going to need my full attention.
We're now going into 3,000 retail
locations in America.
We're in 3,500 in the UK,
coming up to 10 million cans sold.
It's a beast.
And the point of this is,
I'm not a business expert.
I've said this all the time.
The books,
"Sunday Times" number one bestseller.
My coaching app is one of the biggest
ever. Never used paid ads.
Nutonic, scaling it.
This business mentorship made over $5
million in the last two
years. This is what I do.
I take ordinary people, myself,
a skill set that's acquired through
helping businesses, personal training
sessions, or growing businesses,
and I help people grow.
And like I say,
an extra two grand a month for a lot of
you would just be enough
just to take the stress,
just take the burden off.
We even got a payment plan on that.
So you can do two monthly payments of 999.
There's loads of reviews here on the
website.
But ultimately,
the way we're doing things now has been
amazing for two years,
but I can't continue it forever.
I will see out every single
person's Discord duration because there
are some people that bought three months
ago for a year.
So I'll go the whole way through,
but I'm getting too busy.
So you got your offer there, 100 spaces,
six-month sprint.
Because I don't know about you, right?
2026, you probably had some big goals
and ambitions.
We're halfway through,
and it's completely all right
if you're not where you wanted
to be. So I'm saying,
for the next six months, work with me,
my team.
We've got onboarding calls for everyone
that jumps in now.
Talk about your problems.
Building out some new exciting features.
We've got a lot of AI tools that
are in there as well.
Six months,
you get everything you want and more.
And if you don't,
I'll give you fucking cash back.
This is the last sprint, not just for you,
but for me too. 100 spaces.
Take them. Don't take them.
I need to get my life back. All right.
If you're watching this on YouTube,
there's going to be a link in the
description.
If you're watching this on Instagram,
read the prompt below.
[chuckles] It'll tell you what to comment.
All right. It's been good.
It will be good for the next six months.
Then I'm out. Bye-bye.